webcodeexpert.com 2015-12-31

# Terms of Use & Privacy Policy ~ Asp.Net,C#.Net,VB.Net,MVC,jQuery,JavaScipt,AJAX,WCF,Sql Server example

**1\. ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS**

www.webcodeexpert.com provides its service to you, subject to the following Terms of Service. These policies may be updated by us from time to time without notice of you. You can review our updated terms and conditions always in this page. Usage of this site is subject to these Terms, Conditions and Policies, therefore please read the following information carefully.

**2\. USAGE OF THIS SITE**

www.webcodeexpert.com is a technical blog with a motto of sharing technical articles that will be helpful for developers. The purpose of this site is to provide technical information to the programmers and developers. Even though full care has been taken when creating articles, www.webcodeexpert.com doesn’t guarantee the accuracy of the content or information that provided in this site. www.webcodeexpert.com will not be responsible in any way for any damages/consequences that might occur due to inclusion of some incorrect content or information in this site. You can use this information solely at your own risk. All trademarks and company names published in this site are subjected to their respected owners and companies.

**3\. ANTI-SPAM POLICY**

www.webcodeexpert.com is against in sending spam, unsolicited emails. You should not use our service and you are not authorized to use our referral or email services, for your personal or commercial purposes. By usage of this service you agreed that to our policies. Violating these policies in any manner subject to violation of respected laws and necessary action will be initiated against the defaulters.

**4\. COPYRIGHT POLICY**

All pages, data and graphics presented on this website are the property of www.webcodeexpert.com. The pages may not be redistributed or reproduced in any way, shape, or form without the written permission of www.webcodeexpert.com. www.webcodeexpert.com respects the copyrights, trademarks and intellectual property of others and also we expect this from other users. In this site, if you found any information that is owned by you or any content that violates your intellectual property rights, please contact to us with all necessary documents/information that authenticate your authority on your property.

**5\. PRIVACY POLICY**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at lalit24rocks@gmail.com.

At www.webcodeexpert.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.webcodeexpert.com and how it is used.

**Cookies and Web Beacons  
**www.webcodeexpert.com does not use cookies.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie  **  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.webcodeexpert.com.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.webcodeexpert.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....  
Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.webcodeexpert.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.webcodeexpert.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.webcodeexpert.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
